{"questions":[{"question":"Product Backlog should be ordered on the basis of?","level":"1","answers":["Value of the items being delivered","The complexity of the items being delivered","The risk associated with the items","Based on the Scrum Team choice"],"team":"animal","correct_ans":1},{"question":"What should be the size of the Development Team?","level":"1","answers":["5+-3","7+-1","6+-4","7+-2"],"team":"animal","correct_ans":4},{"question":"Which of the following is a black box testing strategy?","level":"2","answers":["All Statements Coverage","Control Structure Coverage","Cause-Effect Graphs ","All Paths Coverage"],"team":"animal","correct_ans":3},{"question":"In an Agile environment, what is the main responsibility of a tester?","level":"1","answers":["Create test scenarios and test cases","Finding bugs","Create automation scripts","There is no role as a Tester in Scrum "],"team":"animal","correct_ans":4},{"question":" A set of inputs, execution preconditions and expected outcomes is known as a","level":"1","answers":["Test plan","Test Case","Test Document","Test Suite"],"team":"animal","correct_ans":2},{"question":" What do you understand by V&V in software testing?","level":"1","answers":["Verified Version","Version Validation","Verification and Validation","Version Verification"],"team":"animal","correct_ans":3},{"question":"What does MDE stand for ?","level":"2","answers":["Multiple Data Entry","Model Driven Engineering ","Machine Design Engineering","Modular Design Environment"],"team":"animal","correct_ans":2},{"question":"Which of the following isn't a Type of Model Driven Architecture ?","level":"3","answers":["CIM - Computation Independent Model","PIM - Platform Infepedent Model","CIV - Computation Independent Viewpoint","PSM - Platform Specific Models"],"team":"animal","correct_ans":3},{"question":" Which of the following isn't a participant in the Inspection group ?","level":"1","answers":["Moderator","Tester","HR Manager","Author"],"team":"animal","correct_ans":3},{"question":" Peer Reviews are also called as : ","level":"2","answers":["Inspection","Technical Review","Walkthrough","Formal Review"],"team":"animal","correct_ans":2},{"question":"Most of the times, in order to find the fault, maintenance programmer must have: source code and:","level":"2","answers":["The time it was discovered.","The fault report filed by user.","Reports of similar faults.","Patience"],"team":"animal","correct_ans":2},{"question":"Internal consistency is :","level":"3","answers":["Designing operations in an application.","Designing operations, interfaces, etc., to be the same across applications and devices.","Difficult to achieve with complex interfaces","Data written to the database of the application must be valid according to all defined rules."],"team":"animal","correct_ans":3},{"question":"Which of the following is not a Usability goal when designing?","level":"1","answers":["Effictive.","Efficient.","Easy to remember how to use.","Visibility."],"team":"animal","correct_ans":4},{"question":"which of the following is true ragarding design Constraints:","level":"3","answers":["Physical objects can be designed to constrain things.","Constraining enumerates the possible values of a set of variables may take in a given world.","Specifies rules for the data in a table.","Constraint module offers solvers for Constraint Satisfaction Problems(CSP)."],"team":"animal","correct_ans":1},{"question":"The Hierarchy of consumer needs(Top,Middle,Bottom):","level":"2","answers":["Usability, Pleasure, Functionality.","Pleasure, Functionality, Usability.","Functionality, Pleasure, Usability.","Pleasure, Usability,Functionality."],"team":"animal","correct_ans":4},{"question":"which of the following is a Lehman law?","level":"3","answers":["Extra resources must be devoted to preserve the structre of an evolving program.","Real world environment program becomes less usful if it goes through a change.","The functionality offered by systems must stop increment to keep the system simple.","The quality of systems will decline unless they are modified to reflect changes in their operational environment."],"team":"animal","correct_ans":4}]}